RG 062:160, Town of Willington
Connecticut State Library
Town of Willington records
1823-1929
Connecticut State Library
Willington (Conn.)
10 cubic feet
Administrative and tax records for the town of Willington.
RG062_160
T000657
Historical Note
The town of Willington was incorporated in May 1727.
Scope and Content
Administrative and tax records for the town of Willington.
Index Terms
Subjects:
Tax assessment -- Connecticut -- Willington -- Registers; Taxation -- Connecticut -- Willington -- Registers; Local taxation -- Connecticut -- Willington -- Registers; Property tax -- Connecticut -- Willington -- Registers
Places:
Willington (Conn.) -- Records and correspondence
Restrictions on Access
These records are stored at an off-site facility and therefore may not be available on a same-day basis.
See the policy.
Container List
- Records, 1823-1929
  - Tax abstracts, 1823, 1826-1853 (Box Box 1)
  - Assessment list, School District 8, 1858 (Box Box 2)
  - Notice of payment for "Children of Deceased Soldiers", 1868 (Box Box 2)
  - Tax abstracts
    Tax abstracts for 1915 to 1929 are not boxed.
    - 1854, 1855, 1856, 1857, 1857 appendix, 1858, 1859 (Box Box 3)
    - 1860, 1861, 1862, 1863, 1864, 1865, 1866, 1867, 1869 (Box Box 4)
    - 1870, 1871, 1872, 1873, 1874, 1876, 1877, 1878, 1879 (Box Box 5)
    - 1880, 1881, 1882, 1883, 1884, 1885 (Box Box 6)
    - 1886, 1887, 1888, 1889, 1890, 1891, 1892 (Box Box 7)
    - 1893, 1894, 1895, 1896, 1897 (Box Box 8)
    - 1898, 1899, 1900, 1901, 1902 (Box Box 9)
    - 1904, 1905, 1906, 1907, 1908 (Box Box 10)
    - 1909, 1910, 1911, 1912, 1913, 1914 (Box Box 11)
      On oversize shelving.
    - 1915, 1 volume
    - 1916, 1 volume
    - 1917, 1 volume
    - 1918, 1 volume
    - 1919, 1 volume
    - 1920, 1 volume
    - 1921, 1 volume
    - 1922, 1 volume
    - 1923, 1 volume
    - 1924, 1 volume
    - 1925, 1 volume
    - 1926, 1 volume
    - 1927, 1 volume
    - 1928, 1 volume
    - 1929, 1 volume